efbet.com 2012-10-05

# Rules - Privacy Policy - EFbet - The game goes on!

**Eurofootball Limited** is a company performing business as an on-line bookmaker, incorporated and licensed in the Republic of Malta in February 2006, listed under registration No. C 40842 and based in the Republic of Malta.

**Eurofootball Limited** holds a Class 2 license issued by the Lotteries and Gaming Authority of the Republic of Malta to operate in the world wide web as an international sports bookmaker.

We grant access to playing games of Sports Book through high security networks using encryption of the user name and the password.

The users of the website EFbet.com may not use Sports Book for any commercial purposes or on behalf of another person. Each using of Sports Book, Poker or the Casino Games by you is only for your own private purposes.

Users shall keep the confidentiality of their user name, ID and password, and shall not disclose them to anybody. Users shall not use other people’s user name, user ID and password for access to the website. You shall be responsible for all transactions made in respect of your player account in which your user name and password for access to the website have been used. The responsibility for all operations and transactions, made with your username and password as well as for all liabilities, resulting from them, is all yours.

It shall be your responsibility to make sure that you fully understand the rules and procedures of the games in Sports Book, Poker and the Casino Games, and your using of on-line gambling as a whole, before you play such games.

We are using the best methods available today for the encryption of the username and password, as well as any other sensitive information transferred to and from the client application and our servers, thus ensuring the user’s and our own security against manipulation attempts by third parties. Users shall not be entitled to break in, access or attempt to break in or access or otherwise by-pass the established rules on security. If we have a suspicion that a user has attempted to or may attempt to violate the rules on security, access or otherwise by-pass the established rules on security or Software, we will be entitled to terminate with immediate effect your access to the Sports Book and Casino Games and/or have your account blocked, and we reserve the right to inform the applicable authorities

We will only use your personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy, which is set out in full at the website of EFbet.com. The company reserves the right to amend the Privacy Policy at any time. However, Efbet.com reserves the right to ask you to provide us with additional details and any such additional information will be kept confidential. We further reserve the right under certain circumstances to disclose certain details to relevant authorities should this be required by law, a state or a regulatory body. The subject of the provisions of the privacy policy is the right to disclose personal information to bodies or authorities whose purpose is to investigate money laundering, fraud and other criminal activity, and such information will be limited to the extent required by law.

As the operating company of the website www.EFbet.com, Eurofootball Limited aims to actively work towards enhancing trust in data protection and thus takes all possible steps to inform its users of all relevant security measures.

In order to place real time bets through the website EFbet.com, you must first register in our database and therewith provide the following personal data:

* Gender

* Proper name and family name

* Date of birth

* Residence

* E-mail 

* Confirmation that you are over 18 years old

*Confirmation that you give Eurofootball Limited the right to use any means, it considers necessary to confirm your identity.

**When you wish to deposit funds to your user account by means of a credit card, the following data will be required:**

* Proper name and family name of the card holder (in the same way as inscribed on the face of your card)

* Name of the bank issuing the credit card

* Number of the credit card

* Expiry date of the credit card

**When you wish to transfer your winnings to your bank account, the following personal data will be required:**

* Proper name and family name of the account holder

* Name of the bank

* IBAN

* SWIFT

Before authorization of your first dividend, you will be asked to send us a copy of an official document containing your photograph (such as a passport, ID document), by fax or scanned and sent to us via e-mail. 

All personal data are stored in the company’s database. People e.g. Customer support and/or Risk/Payment Manager in **Eurofootball Limited**  have access to all personal data stored in the company’s database.

Supply of personal data to third parties is on an opt-in basis in case of direct marketing.

**Eurofootball Limited**  takes protection of data extremely seriously and complies with the data protection act. We are committed to respecting customer privacy. This Privacy and Site Usage policy sets out our data processing practices carried out through the use of the Internet and the World Wide Web. 

**Disclosures**

We will not disclose personal information to other companies or associated or subsidiary companies and to business partners, However we may inform you (by e-mail, telephone, text message, mail or otherwise) about products and services (including those of other companies and organisations) that we consider may be of interest to you.
